Not that way!
Help her! Quick!
It's pointless.
Don't bother.
Maybe it is, but I can't just do nothing!
Hey!
Stop!
Don't butt in!
Did you think you could just take my loot?
What did I tell you?
There's no point in helping her.
Just who is she, anyway?
An oddball who shows up
like the wind, literally,
wherever there are rare magical beasts.
Ow!
A freak who fights using
her mastery of bizarre tools.
She may look sweet,
but she's a problem child
unlike any this kingdom's ever seen.
And that hair color she doesn't bother
to hide makes it easy to guess her status.
That's why they call her...
the plundering princess of the hunt:
the "Marauder Princess."
There we go.
Okay, so I'll be taking all of the
materials from the beasts I killed.
Of course.
You saved us a lot of trouble,
Princess. We appreciate it.
It's no trouble!
I wanted the materials, anyway.
It's win-win!
Oh, uh...
That means both sides come out on top,
so everybody's smiling!
Yay, yay! Y'know?
Ah, right. That is good, indeed.
Let's hope both sides come out
smiling every time we meet.
Sure! You can count on me!
Every magician should use their
magic to make others smile.
That's the kind of magician I want to be!
W-Well, thanks for everything!
She's an unusual sort of princess.
Right?
She's royalty, and yet she's
a high-ranking adventurer.
Some crazy kinda princess, huh?
That, too, but if she's royalty,
she could just use magic.
So why does she use those weird tools?
Oh...
Because she...
can't use magic.
The Magical Revolution
of the Reincarnated Princess and the Genius Young Lady
Regarding your upcoming schedule...
As was discussed in the court council,
there is a document seeking
approval for tax reforms.
Yes, I know.
I'll take care of it today.
Prince Algard, if you would read it, as well...
A-Anis—
Father! And Al! Hey there!
Sister...
You fool!
How does one get so filthy
first thing in the morning?!
You've been hunting for materials again?
Have you no awareness of your role
as princess, you foolish girl?!
I-I'm sorry! Please don't hit me!
Corporal punishment in the name
of discipline is abuse! It's DV!
It's illegal! Criminal! You'll be held liable!
Forced to resign! The kingdom will suffer!
Wh-What in the world are you talking about?
Yes! I argued him down! Now's my chance!
That fool daughter of mine...
Hmm...
What is it?
The hide of a gray wolf.
I've heard ordinary swords
can't even scratch them.
How did she skin it so cleanly?
The Mana Blade that Her Highness
crafted is dreadfully sharp.
The study of magical science
that Her Highness advocates...
"Magicology," was it?
It is indeed a thing to be feared.
Most impressive of her.
I swear...
That foolish daughter of mine is
always so bloody unpredictable!
Just the other day, she said she was
inventing some new magical tool,
and then she burned down
half of the royal villa!
Both His Majesty and the prime minister
are too soft on that insane princess.
Yes, but she did renounce
her right to the throne.
She can't cause any real harm
holed up in the royal villa.
But if that shady magicology
of hers gets around,
it may decimate the dignity of the nobility.
Still, magicology could be of use to us.
If she actually has a knack
for magic, it could mean...
Hmph. A simpleton who can't even
use magic is nothing to us.
You've really done it this time, I see.
Well, some unexpected stuff happened.
If you ask me, you yourself are an
entire bundle of "unexpected."
It was when you were five
years old, wasn't it?
When you said out of nowhere
that you wanted to fly.
If I had magic, I could fly...
With magic... I could fly?
The Witch and the Flying Broom
Princess!
You mustn't run in the corridors.
Let me go! I just remembered something!
I have to ask Father!
Ask him for what?
To use magic to fly!
Ever since then, you've done all kinds
of reckless things in your pursuit of flight.
I did, didn't I?
Just how many brooms have been
sacrificed for your cause?
I sacrificed another one today.
I'll have to get a replacement.
It's good of you to worry about the broom,
but you should worry
about yourself, as well.
Thanks.
You're the only one who
understands me, Ilia.
Yes, I understand you
exceedingly well, Princess.
Fantasies about things like being able
to fly are very common during puberty.
Indeed, I understand.
Okay, you don't get it at all.
What will you do now?
If you will be going out,
I will attend to your hair.
Yeah, please do. I'm going to see Tilty.
To perform an examination?
Nope, today we're discussing medication.
Ah...
That matter.
You've brought another enormous
piece of magicite, I see.
Right? We should be able to make even
more effective medicine from this!
Well, I suppose we can try it.
You said you use this
medicine when fighting.
The side effects don't bother you?
Not at all!
At most, you might get a little hyper,
and it might be a little addictive.
Your use of "a little" is hilariously scary.
You want to use magic so badly
that you'd get your hands on this?
You really are crazy.
There's no other way, though.
I was born without the ability to use magic.
And I'm royalty! Can you believe it?
It makes things kinda tough.
I don't see the problem.
Magic isn't that big a deal.
That's not true!
Magic is fantastic! Magic is the best!
Magic is romantic!
"Romantic" again?
You're talking about absurd
fantasies like flying, right?
Yeah, exactly!
Wait, "fantasies"? What?
I'd say your doom-and-gloom hobby
of collecting curses is way more absurd.
Well, for me, it's just a hobby.
I'm not trying to do it
for anyone else's sake.
But you...
You're doing your research because
you want to make people smile, right?
Y-Yeah, that's right.
Jeez, where'd that come from?
You're making me blush.
I'd call that statement
an absurd fantasy, too.
Huh?
So? Can you fly now?
No, I can still only manage low altitudes.
But if I increase the output,
I think I can go higher!
If I just shove in even more spirit stones...
But the safety measures
that would require...
What even made you think of doing
something so needlessly dangerous
as flying with magic?
What? Haven't you ever wanted to fly?
You're a maverick princess in every
possible way, you know that?
This kingdom's in real trouble
with a princess like you.
What? I don't want to hear
that from a noble lady
who went berserk and almost destroyed
a marquess's household.
Okay?
Anyway, don't worry about my family!
We've got Al, so we're totally fine!
The royal family's in good hands!
Oh, right. I heard your
brother's getting married.
What do you think of his fiancée,
the genius daughter of Duke Magenta?
She's pretty.
That's all you can say?
Well, I haven't really spoken with her.
Oh? I thought the duke's family
and the royal family went way back.
You've never seen her?
Well... I was pretty young at the time, so...
I don't really remember.
Oh, so herbal tea is all
the rage in the castle town?
Yes.
We make it from herbs
we've picked ourselves.
Really? I'd love to have some with you soon.
What? Oh, but... it's really nothing special...
Lady Lainie is with Prince Algard again.
I don't mind. The time spent with
you is what gives it meaning.
Wasn't she born a commoner?
Listening to your stories gives me peace.
Yes. Her father was granted the rank
of baron for his distinguished service.
Well, that is lovely.
But for her to spend all her time with
people as high-ranking as the prince...
Yes, not to mention that
the prince is betrothed,
and he'll be graduating soon.
I'm sure he's merely being courteous
to Baron Cyan's daughter.
I think being considerate of school friends
is a very admirable trait for a royal to have.
Y-Yes, you're right.
If that's what you say, Lady Euphyllia,
then it's absolutely true!
You're still here?
I've been waiting for you.
You really went to a lot of trouble.
Everyone knows this marriage
is strictly political.
What's the point of a tea party?
Formalities such as this are essential
precisely because it is political.
We need to build mutual trust
and knowledge of each other.
As the ones who will inherit the kingdom—
As usual, you're so perfect, it's disgusting.
I am merely trying to
fulfill my role as a noble.
Hah. Nobility? Worthless.
Your Highness, please refrain from
behaving that way here at the castle.
No, not only at the castle.
At the academy, as well.
The academy?
What are you getting at?
I said the same thing to
Baron Cyan's daughter,
but I would like you to
bear it in mind, as well.
You and I are betrothed.
To avoid causing unwanted rumors,
I believe you should choose
your friends carefully.
As if we have the right to choose
anything for ourselves.
But your advice is valuable.
I'll accept it with gratitude.
You can just let me choose
who's worthy of being with me.
What do you mean?
Do I really have to spell it out?
I thought a duke's genius daughter,
the noblest noble around,
would pick up easily on insinuations.
Are we done?
Looks like we both wasted our time.
The brooms in the castle
really are the best around!
Just look at this! Isn't it great?
You truly do love brooms, don't you?
Yeah, I do!
I love them so much,
I swept away my right to the throne!
No one is going to laugh at that.
A-Al! This isn't what it looks like!
I'm not stealing it!
I was just cleaning the...
That rebellious phase...
Weather: perfect!
Wind speed: perfect!
Gear: all set!
Safety checks: complete!
It's the perfect night for experimenting!
Please wait a moment.
It's quite cold out tonight.
Ooh, you're the best, Ilia! Thanks!
Please remember,
you mustn't go too high or too fast.
If anything goes wrong...
I know, I know. You worry too much.
Of course I'm going to worry.
I can't allow anything
to happen to our princess,
and above all, you can't use magic,
so if anything happens
in the air, you won't be—
Well, I'm off! Have some hot tea
waiting when I get back!
As you wish, Princess.
I'm really flying!
My dream from my previous
life has come true!
I'm so glad we made it to graduation.
Yeah, really. I almost got
held back for lack of credits.
You're going back home
after graduation, right?
So this is our last soirée at this academy.
Indeed. We are graduating, after all.
So the rumor was true.
Yeah. Her personality's so
overwhelming that the prince...
Duke Magenta's daughter is here alone?
What about the prince?
The prince... Wait, that can't be...
Oh, my goodness! Look at who he's escorting!
Everyone, congratulations on graduating.
I'm pleased to have arrived
at this occasion with all of you.
This is a joyous day for celebrating
the start of our new lives,
but there is something
I need to say to all of you.
I hereby declare that I am calling off
my engagement to Euphyllia Magenta!
The prince just called off
his own engagement?
But why would Lady Euphyllia...
Prince Algard, why are you
calling off our engagement?
I decided that you are not worthy
of being engaged to me.
You can make no excuses for the many
atrocities you've committed against Lainie!
If you're speaking of the advice
I gave to Lady Lainie,
I meant no ill will against her!
Has the king agreed with your decision?
I'll get my father's approval later.
How could you call off the engagement your
father chose for you without his consent?!
Who should I feel afraid of?
Times change!
I will choose my own path
at my own discretion!
But there are certain standards
to which you must adhere!
Please reconsider!
Have you truly become so blind?
You have the nerve to call me blind?
You are the blind one, Euphyllia!
You want to be queen so badly,
you refuse to see anything else!
That makes you unworthy!
Lainie has endured excessive
bullying, stealing, and harm—
even plans to have her assassinated!
And I know you were behind all of it!
I've told you, I have no idea what—
I can testify.
We have witnessed the many evil deeds
she has orchestrated against Lady Lainie.
Lainie may have been born a commoner,
but the reprehension against her
has been taken too far.
Apparently, she forced her followers
to harass Lady Lainie so that she
wouldn't get her own hands dirty.
What... is going on?
I considered it my duty...
I wanted to set an example for others,
to be strong and righteous as the
future queen and a baron's daughter...
Too bad, Euphyllia.
Repent for all the wrong you've done,
and apologize to Lainie.
I...
Ow... Total control failure...
You're...
Oh, Al! Hiyas!
Sister...
Uh, did I... drop in at a bad time?
Hey, c'mon, Al.
Why are you waiting on another girl
when Lady Euphyllia is right there?
That's none of your business!
Hey, no need to get so angry.
Jeez, he's super pissed.
Talk about scary. What's his deal?
Lady Euphyllia?
So, uh, what's going on?
Is she his prospective
mistress or something?
Wait, did he... call off your engagement?
Oh, man! For real? That actually happens?
All right! I've decided!
I'll take you away!
C'mon, let's go! Right now!
Up you go!
Wh-Wha... Wait! Please put me down!
So anyway, Al...
I'll just take this little story back home.
Wait!
Sister!
W-We're flying?!
Welcome to your journey through
the skies, Lady Euphyllia!
The story you are about to hear
is the story of two young girls
from a certain kingdom.
The story of a princess who loved
magic more than anyone else,
but whom magic did not love in return.
The story of a noble lady
who was born with everything,
but had nothing.
The story of their revolution.
This is the beginning of that story.
Um, where are we going?
To see my father and Duke Grantz.
Why?
Because I'm the Marauder Princess.
I'm gonna ask them to let me have you!
Huh?
What?!
Episode One
The Magical Revolution of the
Princess and the Young Lady
Episode Two
Acquisition of an Assistant
for Both Profit and Pleasure